swellnet.com.au 2018-10-01

# Privacy | Swellnet

## You are here

  1. Home
  2. Privacy policy

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy please direct them to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#95b3b6a4a4a7aeb3b6a4a4a1aeb3b6a4a5a0aeb3b6a4a4adaeb3b6a5aca2aeb3b6a5acacaeb3b6a4a7a4aeb3b6a5a3a1aeb3b6a4a4a0aeb3b6a4a4acaeb3b6a4a5a4aeb3b6a4a5adaeb3b6a4a5adaeb3b6a4a4a5aeb3b6a4a5a4aeb3b6a4a4a3aeb3b6a5a1a3aeb3b6a5acacaeb3b6a4a4a4aeb3b6a4a5acae).

You may also send a letter to: 

> Swellnet Pty Ltd  
>  Level 5, 8 West Street  
>  North Sydney, NSW, 2060  
>  Australia 

  * Swellnet does not sell, exchange, or release your personal information (name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card data, etc.) without your consent to any third parties.
  * When we do give information to our advertisers, it is in the form of grouped statistics compiled from registration data and participants’ answers to survey questions. None of the data provided is personally identifiable.
  * Information gathered through the use of cookies is not related to any personally identifiable details.

### What information does Swellnet collect from our users and how do we collect it?

Swellnet only contacts individuals who specifically request that we do so. Swellnet collects personally identifying information from our users during (1) online registration, (2) online surveys, and (3) online purchasing. Generally, this information includes name, e-mail address, postal address, and answers to survey questions. This information is used for internal marketing purposes and helps us determine how to continually improve our site.

### What are cookies and how do we use them?

Cookies help track a person's "session" while online. They are used on our site to gather basic tracking information and to monitor the presentation of advertisements. Cookies are not related to any personally identifiable information and are not used to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie.

In some instances, advertisers will set cookies on our site. These cookies are not related to any personally identifiable information that we have collected but are for monitoring and tracking ad impressions.

Many browsers are set to accept cookies. You may prefer to set your browser to refuse cookies. It is possible, however, that some areas of the site will not function properly if you do so.

**This policy may be changed at any time at Swellnet's discretion.**
